Guide to the Internation Brotherhood of Teamsters Graphic Communications Conference records, 1902-2006 IBT0006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Graphic Communications Conference records
1902-2006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
IBT0006
36 Linear Feet
This collection contains the records of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Graphic Communications Conference dating from 1902-2006. Specifically it contains Willims Moody's research files when he was editor of the Graphic Communicator, journal of the Graphic Communications International Union. and records of Pressmen's Local 22, Denver, Colorado.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2012 February 29 [2012.028].
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the records of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Graphic Communications Conference dating from 1902-2006. Cuurently, the collection is comprised of William Moody's GCC-GCIU Public Information Department research files and a set of agreements pertaing to Pressmen's LocaL 22, Denver.
Arrangement
Organized into 2 series: GCC-GCIU Public Information Department - William Moody Research files and Pressmen's Local 22, Denver records.
Biographical / Historical
The Graphic Communications Conference of the IBT was established in 2004. It represents workers in the printing, publishing and related industries. The GCC's predecessor organization was the Graphic Communications International Union, established in 1983. The GCIU was the result of a merger between the Graphic Arts International Union and the International Printing and Graphic Communications Union (est. 1973). The merger of the International Brotherhood of Bookbinders (est. 1892) and the Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union (est. 1964) resulted in the formation of the Graphic Arts International Union in 1972.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor; Labor unions; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Brotherhood of Teamsters
- Public Information Department - William Moody Research files, 1902-2006; Series 1; 29.25 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series is comprised of research files compiled by William Moody, editor of the Graphic Communicator,dating from 1902-2006.
  - Acid Rain, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO-general, 1962,1964,1967,1977,1980,1984,1971; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO Building and Construction Trades Department, 1979-1981; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO Convention 1969, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO Convention 1973, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO Convention 1975,1976, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO Council Reports, 1973; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO Council Reports Continued, 1975; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statements, 1974-1981; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - AFL-CIO Food and Beverage Trades Department, 1979; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AFL-CIO Industrial Unions Department, 1967-1983; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AFL-CIO International Affairs Department, 1966,1974,1975; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - AFL-CIO Labor Studies Center, 1975-1977; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO Labor Studies Center Catalogues, 1971-1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO List of Council Members, 1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO Maritime Trades Department, 1969-1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO News Releases, 1969,1972,1975; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO Public Employees Department, 1975,1976,1977,1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - AFL-CIO Resolutions, 1955-1966,1975,1977,1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - AFL-CIO Statements Adopted By, 1969,1970,1972,1973,1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - AFL-CIO Union Label and Service Trade Department - General, 1965-1978, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO Union Label and Service Trade Department - Official News, 1965-1970; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO Union Label and Service Trade Department - Labeletter, 1973-1977; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - AFT Million Dollar Militancy Fund Dinner, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - AIDS Forum, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Alliance for Labor Action, 1969-1970; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Allied Printing Trades Assosication, 1965-1966,1969,1973-1977,1983; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alchoholism, 1976-1977,1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Amalgomated Lithographers of America, 1961-1968,1982,1984; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Amalgomated Society of Lithographic Printers of Great Britain and Ireland, 1967; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1972,1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1975; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - American Newspapers Publishers Association, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - American Photoengravers Association, 1966-1968; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - American Society of Business Press Editors, 1972,1983,1985,1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Americans for Democratic Action, 1966,1978,1980,1983,1987,1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Amnesty International, 1981; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - APA-LPIU Roundtable, 1969; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Apprenticeship and Training Standards - Graphic Arts International Union, 1974,1975; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Are You True To Yourself?" United Garment Workers of America Pamphlet, ND (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Asbestos and Health Information, 1973; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Assosiation of Representitives of Professional Athletes, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Austin Locals 228, 528, 1967,1982-1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Auto Workers United, 1962,1965,1966,1968-1971,1973,1976,1977,1979,1980,1982,1983,1985; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Authors Alterations, 1983; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Automation and Society, the Georgia Reliance Symposium, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Bachman, Gilbert, 1984; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Baltimore Locals 182, 348, 1969, 1981-1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Banta Printing Company, 1972-1974,1979; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bargaining, 1969-1976; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bargaining Conference 1974, Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bargaining Conference 1978, 1977-1978; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Battle Creek 263, 1975; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Bauer, 1971; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Benshop, John J, 1969; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Beine, Ross, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bicentenial, Use of Official Symbol, 1971,1976; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Binders Bulletin, 1972; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Binghamton 89B, 1982; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Black Trade Unionists, 1974; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Boerner, Eugene, 1976,1980,1983; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Boise Cascade, 1983-1985,1987,1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Bonelli, Felicia, 1977-1979,1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - International Bookbinder, 1971,1972; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bookbinder Conferences, Eastern States, 1976; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bookbinders Conferences Mideast, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bookbinder Conferences, South Central, 1975,1980; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Bookbinder Conferences Western, 1975; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bookbinding Historical Material, 1902-1992; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Boston 600, 1980,1983,1984; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bowling Parties, 1967,1976,1979,1982; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Boy Scouts, 1983; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bruttlebord 109B, 1981,1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Brennan, Peter J, 1972,1973; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bricklayers, 1985,1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Brightype, 1962; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Brill, Arthur, 1962; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - British Columbia 525, 1982; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - British Union, 1974,1983; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Brotherhood Railway Clerks, 1973; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Arthur, 1891,1932,1961,1970,1979; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Brown, Kenneth J., 1960-1970; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Brown Kenneth, 1970-1980; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Broyhill, Joel T., 1970; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Buffa, 10 201, 1981,1985,1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Buchwald, joseph on the Issue, 1970,1973; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Bulk Mailing, 1975,1978-1991; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Burrelle's Press Clipping Service, 1964,1965,1967,1978,1982,1985,1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Business Forms Industry, 1971; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cable Programing, 1982; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - California State Printing Plant, Sacramento, 1979; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Canada GAIU, 1979,1982; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Canadian Bargaining, 1983,1985; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Canadian Association of Labor Media, 1979-1985,1987,1989,1990; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Canadian Federation of Printing Trades Unions, 1980,1985,1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Canadian Labor Congress, 1965,1968,1972-1974,1976,1978,1982; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Canadian Labor Congress Protesting Wage Controls, 1976; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Canadian Lithorgraphic Institute, 1969; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Canadian News Service, 1987; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Canadian Policy Conference 1968, 1967,1968; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Canadian Policy Conference 1973, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Canadian Policy Conference 1976, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Canadian Policy Conference 1980, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Canadian Presidents Conference, 1972,1976,1980,1981; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Canadian Presidents Conference Continued, 1974,1978; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Canadian Specialty Conference, 1983,1986; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Canadian Union Autonomy, 1972,1974; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Career Equality for Workers, 1974,1975,1977; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1976; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cartoons, 1978,1988; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Case-Hoyt, 1969; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Charter Forms and Samples for the GAIU, 1972; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Coalition Against PIA, 1978; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Chicago Graphic Arts Institute, 1965,1971,1972,1977; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Chicago Lithographers Institute, 1958,1961,1962,1979; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Chicago 8B, 1973,1975,1978,1980,1981; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Chicago 245, 1966,1969,1971,1977,1980,1981,1983,1984; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Chile, 1974,1983; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - China, 1971,1973; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Cincinnati 271, 1966,1968-1972; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - City of Hope, 1983,1987; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Clarke, Richard J., 1973,1974,1978; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Cleveland 546, 1982-1984,1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Clothing/Textile Workers, 1981; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Coalition of Coalitions, 1978; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974-1984; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Coe, Geoff, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Commins, Raphael F., 1985; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Common Cause, 1973,1974,1977; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Community Television Review, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Compotype Specimen Book, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Reapportionment, 1980; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Congressional Strength of GAIU, 1978; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Constitution and Laws of the Graphic Arts International Union, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Contracts, 1966-1986; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Conventions GAIU - Special Convention, 1973; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Conventions GAIU - Constitutional Convention, 1975; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Conventions GAIU - Constitutional Convention, 1978; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Conventions GAIU - Second Constitutional Convention, 1978; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Conventions GAIU - Third Constitutional Convention, 1981; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Conventions GAIU - Founding Convention, 1984; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Conventions Industrial Union Department AFLCIO Ninth Constitutional Convention, 1971; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Convention - Photoengravers IPEO 1940, 1940,1962; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Convention LPIU - First Constitutional Convention, 1965; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Convention LPIU - Constitutional Convention, 1967; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Convention LPIU - Constitutional Convention, 1969; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Convention LPIU - Constitutional Convention, 1969; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Convention LPIU - Constitutional Convention, 1971; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Cooperative Press Association, 1970; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cope Collections, 1969,1972,1973,1979; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Copyright Law, 1971,1977,1983; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cornelius Printing, 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Cost of Living, 1970-1971; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Cotton, Eugene, 1975; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Council of Printing Industries of Canada, 1979; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Council on Hemispheric Affairs, 1981-1982; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Counseling Program Guide, 1979; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Craston, Alan, 1983; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Credit Unions, 1970; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - CRT, 1976; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Curran, Joe, 1973,1981; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Curtis Publishing Campaign, 1966; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Danbury Hatters PAI - Article, 1970; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Daycare, 1983; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Dayton 275, 1972; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Dayton press 199B, 1980-1982,1985; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Debs Papers Project, 1974,1979,1982; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - DeGennaro, Patrick, 1987; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Delong, Hal, 1982; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Democratic Party, 1974,1976; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Democratic Study Group on Proposed Welfare Reform, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Dente: Promises and Pitfalls by Gerald Steibel, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Denver 440, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Denver 570, 1965,1971,1981,1983; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Department of Labor, 1988; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Des moines 86C, 1986; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Detroit 2C, 1984-1987; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Detroit 289, 1979-1981; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Diehl, Oscar, 1970,1971; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Dillon, Henry J., 1964-1966,1968,1970-1972,1976,1977; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Disabled, 1966; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - District 1199, 1985,1986; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - District Coucil 2, 1987; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Diversified Printing Corporation, 1979; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Donahue, Edward V., 1970,1972,1974,1976,1978,1981; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - donahue, Thomas R. Histadrut Award, 1981-1982; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Donnelly and Sons Company, 1967,1972,1973,1977,1985; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Donahue, mary Ann, 1977; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Douglas, Thomas Clement, 1986; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - DRUPA, 1968,1986; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Dupont, 1970,1971,1976,1980; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1970; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Economic Policy Institute, 1987; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Editing, 1980,1981; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Edition booklanding Industry, 1975; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Editorial Procedure, 1964-1966; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Education Training and Retraining, 1972,1980; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Effingham 39B, 1986; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Elections - General, 1968,1970; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Elections - Continued, 1972,1977,1984; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Elections - Continued, 1980; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Elections - GAIU, 1976,1985; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Elections - GCIU, 1983-1985; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Elections - LPIU, 1965; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Electoral College, 1977; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Electrical Worker (IUE) re Carey and Hartnett, 1962; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Employee Stock Ownership Plans, 1983-1987; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Employer Retirement Fund, 1976,1982,1983; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Energy, 1976,1977,1980,1981; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Environment, 1978; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1976,1978; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Equality, 1973,1975,1978; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Ethics Committee, 1975-1983; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Eugene 116C, 1984; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Evansville 571, 1970-1972,1976,1977,1979,1982-1986; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Evergreen 530, 1972,1980-1984; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Farm Workers, United Farm Workers Boycott and Strike, 1968-1979; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - FBI, 1975; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1980; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Festival of American Folk Life, 1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Films - Labor and Other, 1970,1972,1979; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Financial Reports - LPIU, 1963,1971; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Flayler, Jack, 1973; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Flight Log, 1983; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Trade Boycott, 1970,1971,1975,1981; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Fortune 500 Companies, 1975; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Four Day Week, 1971,1972,1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1975; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Full Employment, 1970-1981; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Gananian, Leo - Letter To The Editor, 1970; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - GCIU International Trade Union Guidelines on Visual Display Units, 1985 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Goazglass, Martin R., 1974,1978,1983,1985,1987; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Garn, Jake (Sen), 1979; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Gast, Joseph H., 1987; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - German Trade Union, 1978; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Gompers, Samuel - Hennins Article, 1984; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Government Printing Office, 1975-1977,1981; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Graphic Arts Institute, 1967-1984; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Graphic Arts International Union Constitution and Laws, 1972,1976,1979; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Graphic Arts International Union Contract and Research Department Reports, 1975,1976; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Graphic Arts International Union Graphic Arts Unionist - Picture Survey, 1964-1965; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Graphic Arts International Union Membership Stats, 1976; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Graphic Arts International Union Scholorships, 1972; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - GAIU - Staff Training, 1977,1980; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Graphic Arts Technical Foundation, 1974,1977,1980; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Graphic Arts Unionist. November-December, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Graphic Arts Workers, 1975; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Graphic Communication International Union - General Board Meeting - minutes july 12-14 1983, Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Graphic Communications Technologies and History, 1970,1971; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Graphic Communications World, 1983; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Gravure Technical Association, 1974; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Green,Jack, 1983,1985; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Grievances, 1973-1975; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Gutherie, Woddy, 1976; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Hall, William J., 1962-1976; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Hamilton 542M, 1981-1986; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Hannibal Strike, 1973; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Hartman, Peter E., 1986; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Hawaii, 1970,1978; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Haymarket Memorial, 1970; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Healthcare, Industry, 1985; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Health/Welfare Insurance, 1973; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Helms, Jesse, 1981; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Hill,Joe, 1979,1980,1986; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - History - Labor, 1972-1981; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - History - GAIU, 1900,1974-1976,1982; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Hoffa, James R. - Meet The Press Interview - Letter by Fitz, 1967,1973; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Hollomon, John H., Undated; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Homefront Institute for American Democracy, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Horan Engraving Company, 1968; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Hormel Strike, 1986; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Houston Organizing Project, 1983; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Houstan 265, 1982-1986; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Human rights Commission (DC), 1971; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - IAM Media Project- TV Trainers Manual, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Independent Association of Publishers' Employees, Inc, 1985; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Indianapolis 11P, 1982-1986; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - IRA (Individual Retirement Accounts), 1982; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Inflation, 1975; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Inland Printing, 1968,1969,1971-1973; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Inter Local Pension Fund, 1961,1965,1966,1972,1974,1978,1987; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Inter Local Pension Fund Continued, 1983; Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Inter Local Pension Fund Continued, 1983; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - International Allied Printing Trades Association, 1955,1967; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Labor News, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - International Comprint, 1971; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1985; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - International Consultative Conference of Trade Unions of the Graphic Industry, Budapest, May 12-14 1981, Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans, 1973,1975,1976,1978,1984; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - International Graphical Federation, 1972; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - International Press Association - International Labor Communication Association, 1967,1983,1991,1992; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - IP and GCU Employer Retirement Fund, 1980; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Jackson, J.A., 1967; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - IPEU 50th Anniversary Commemorative Book Milwaukee Photo Engravers Union No. 19, 1951 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - John Birch Society Group Research Report, 1983; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - John Herling's Labor Letter, 1975-1985; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Kansas City 235, 1982-1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Kennedy, Edward, 1979,1980; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1968; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Keylines, 1973-1979; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Kheel, Theodore W., 1968; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - King, Martin Luther Jr., 1968,1985,1986; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)